sscbankrecruitment.in 2016-11-02

# Privacy Policy & Disclaimer at SSCBankRecruitment.in

**Privacy Policy of sscbankrecruitment.in**

The privacy of our website visitors is of great importance to us. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information which is received & collected by www.sscbankrecruitment.in and how it is used. The privacy policy document here we afford for intimating you about how we work on our education & jobs website. This portal provides the employment news gathered from various websites, newspapers. So, when one who is applying for a job or about to attend any interview, based on the information provided in our website is requested to verify the same from different portals or from the official websites. We do not assure that the information provided here is entirely correct. One can use the information at their own risk. We are not responsible for any consequences that occur on applying for any job or walk-in interview information that we provided in our website.

 **Disclaimer:**

sscbankrecruitment.in is website created as a resource to help people know about latest recruitment events, entrance exams, exam results, answer key or solutions, admit cad/hall ticket etc. The site primarily focused on Government jobs in India, bank jobs, railway jobs, private jobs, exam results, admit card, answer key, previous question papers, exam syllabus, admissions, entrance exams and lot more stuff. It is a great platform for job seekers without getting involved in legal suits. So, here is the disclaimer policy for www.sscbankrecruitment.in, Utmost care is generally taken while we are publishing the information in our website. Our source of collecting information is completely from other websites/news papers. There might be some mistakes in our blog which are made unknowingly because the effort is made completely by humans.

Click any link at your own risk in our portal. We are not responsible for any loss you get on doing so. We don’t have control on the portal as these are maintained by third party people. The Job seekers are advised to be careful and check the information from other websites and make conform regarding any particular advertisement.

 **Privacy Policy:**

If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us by email at support@sscbankrecruitment.in, the privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information is received and collected by www.sscbankrecruitment.in and how it is used.

Logos that we use in our portal are completely collected from other websites and sometimes from the official website. We provide it for more interactive to the topic that we are providing in our portal. There is no other intention in providing the logos. Owners of the logo, please write to us if you feel that we are violating the copy write of your logo. We assure you that the logo will be removed in short span of time.

 **Log Files:**

Like many other Web sites, sscbankrecruitment.in makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.

 **Double Click DART Cookie:**

Google as a third party vendor uses cookies to serve ads on www.sscbankrecruitment.in

Google use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to sscbankrecruitment.in and other sites on the Internet.  
Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.  
Google Adsense These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on sscbankrecruitment.in send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies (such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see. sscbankrecruitment.in has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. sscbankrecruitment.in privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites. If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers’ respective websites.

 **Last Modified: 28th July 2015.**
